to
life Welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the CH Commandments
that God commanded the whole world to
keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou not
make unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for the Lord thy God am a
jealous God busit the iniquities of of
the fathers upon the children until the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou not take the name of
the Lord thy God in vain for the Lord
will not hold him Guiltless that take up
his name in vain remember the Sabbath
day to keep his holy six days shall thou
lab and do all thy work but the seventh
day is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God
in it thou shall not do any work thou
nor thy son nor thy daughter thy man
servant nor thy maid servant nor thy
cattle nor thy stranger that is within
thy gates for six days the Lord made
Heaven and Earth the sea and all that in
them is and rested the seventh day
wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day and holled it honor thy father and
thy mother that thy days may be long
upon the land which the Lord thy God
giveth thee thou shall not kill thou
shall not commit adultery thou sh not
steal thou sh not bear false witness
against thy neighbor thou not cover thy
neighbor's house thou not cover thy
neighbor's wife nor his man's servant
nor his maid's servant nor his Ox nor
his ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors we read Exodus
21-17 and may the Lord have a blessing
to the reading of his word
in Jesus name we pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all vague questions will not be answered
and all long scripture questions will
not be answered for time sake but we may
be able to point you in the direction of
a CD or dvd that you can purchase by
call in the office so please be as
direct as possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers out of the King James Bible
no other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we're just asking that you keep
your questions to a two scripture
maximum but let me in introduce to you
the family that's on the panel this
evening we got brother Jerome Grace and
peace Brother Dre good evening brother
Julius good evening everybody brother
tanzel good
evening sister
Deborah good
evening and we have Casey and the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deborah what is our first
question of the evening
uh we have several questions that will
be answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A so uh philosophy asks why
does Paul tell Timothy women are not to
be saved by
childbearing what if you do not bear
children at all in your lifetime does
that mean you'll never be saved in 1
Timothy 2 verse1 15 is given all right
let's go to 1 Timothy 2 and 15 tanzel
and we're going to ask the guest caller
to share some light on this question
about women ought to be saved by
childbearing all right okay go read
notwithstanding she shall be saved and
childbearing if they continue in faith
and charity and holiness with s
sobriety now that didn't say she was
going to be cut off but look what El
Paul said let's go into 1 Corinthians
the 7th chapter and read
6-9 1 Corinthians
76-9 but I speak but I speak this by
permission and not of commandment
why would that all men were even as I
myself but every man have his proper
gift of God one not this manner and
another after that but I say therefore
to the unmar and widows it is good for
them if they abide even as I but if they
cannot contain let them marry for it is
better to marry than to
burn now if you w you wasn't going to be
saved unless you had children then why
is Paul telling the the men and the
women not got to get married that mean
they can't have
children just like he said that is by
permission so with that first Timothy
there ain't nothing in Prophecy said a
woman had to have a child to be
saved and the book say you have to out
of the mouth of two or more witnesses is
the fact of estabished and there ain't
nothing else in the Bible that say a
woman have to have a children to be
saved so all I have to
say all right hope that answers your
question there we continue to move on to
our next next one daughter of Judah says
I was taught the Rapture wasn't biblical
because Christ will be coming back to
his kingdom on Earth but people have
quoted Verses first Thessalonians 4
verse 16 and 17 Matthew 24: 4 and 41 and
Luke 17: 34 and 35 to me is proof of a
Rapture what are the verses referring to
do we want to be left or
taken all right daughter of Judah you
went over our two scripture maximum but
we're going to ask uh brother Julius to
share some light on that
question you were you were talk Cor
corly the word rapture is not even in
the Bible it is not biblical it was
invented and conceived by of Jesuit
priest by in in the 1500s named
Francisco rera I'm gon say that name
again Francisco rera a Jesuit priest who
was commissioned by Pope 6us I to come
up with a counter teaching because the
Catholic Church uh was known that the
head of the Catholic church was known to
be the Antichrist the office of the
Antichrist uh Martin Luther and all
those uh Reformation uh uh preachers
knew about that and that's why they was
excommunicated from the church so now
that happened in the 1500s during a
Reformation so to hide that Sixers
commission francisa rera and another
Jesuit priest to come up with a counter
teaching to throw the people off of the
uh the pope being the head or the
holding the office of antichrist let and
all the scriptures that you named first
Thessalonians the 4th chapter Matthew
the 24th chapter and Luke the 17th
chapter each one of them talks about the
coming of the Lord or what we call which
will be the first resurrection that's
what you get your shall be taken and the
other left let's go and let's look at
what Jesus said because you not getting
off this Earth let's look at what the
Lord what say you going to meet the Lord
in the clouds let's go to first
Thessalonians I go to here and then I
got one scripture after this first
Thessalonians the 4th
chapter and what we don't do at the
Israel of God we don't go by what we
believe we go by what's
written 1 Thessalonians 4 and pick it up
at 14 uh brother
tzel go ahead and read it but if we
believe that Jesus died rose again even
so them also which sleep in Jesus will
God bring with him all right he going to
bring them with him well he going to get
them from in other uh scripture we can
show you goingon to get up from the
grave and those who are changed that
coming verse
15 for this we say unto you by the word
of the Lord that we which are alive and
remain until the coming of the Lord what
until what until the coming of the Lord
all these scriptures deal with the
coming of the Lord the second coming of
Jesus Christ continue shall not prevent
them which are asleep uhhuh for the Lord
himself shall descend from heaven with
the Shout with the voice of the arch
angel and with the Trump of God and the
dead in Christ shall rise first those
seven trumpets got to sound this is the
seventh trumpet which is announces the
second coming of the Lord continue the
dead in Christ gonna rise first go ahead
then we which are alive and remain shall
be caught up together with them in the
clouds to meet the Lord in the air and
so shall we ever be with the Lord so now
everybody the Rapture is predicated off
of the word caught up together with them
in the clouds you're not going to heaven
you're just gonna be a part of the
second heaven but right he said and so
shall we ever be with the Lord nobody
ever answers the question where right
first of all let's go into the first
chapter real quick Acts chapter one and
we going to read verse one let's look at
what the book
says acts one and pick it up at verse
n Look what Jesus this is uh uh the uh
the book of the acts and verse n Go
ahead and when he had spoken these
things while they beheld he was taken up
in a cloud receive him out of their
sight go ahead and while they look
steadfast towards heaven as he went up
behold two men stood by them in white
apparel and these were two angels go
ahead and read it and which also said ye
men of Galilee why stand ye gazing up
into heaven the same Jesus which is
taken up from you into heaven shall so
come in like manner as ye have seen him
go up into heaven so he left from the
mountain Mount of Olives now let's go to
the last scripture let's see what he
coming back to Zechariah the 14th
chapter
the Rapture is is a definition which
means to be taken away or removed
violently and it's also uh the title of
a
uh ferocious uh
bird Zechariah 14 my brother Zechariah
14 and pick it up at verse one then
we'll
skip go ahead and read it behold the day
of the Lord come and thy spoils shall be
divided in the midst of thee so now
we're talking about again the coming of
the Lord the day of the Lord this is
when the Lord begin to come back to this
earth skip down to verse uh three go
ahead then shall the Lord go forth and
fight against those Nations as when he
fought in the day of battle uhhuh and
his feet shall stand in that day upon
the Mount of ol which is before
Jerusalem on the East and the Mount of
ol shall cleave in the midst thereof
towards the east and towards the west
and there shall be a very great Valley
and half of the mountain shall remove
toward the North and half of it towards
the South so when Jesus feet touched
this Earth he going to touch the Mount
of Olives which is exactly where he left
from and it's going to bust open into
four different places north south east
and west continue verse five and ye
shall flee to the Valley of the
mountains for the Valley of the
mountains shall reach unto Asel yeah ye
shall flee like as he fled from before
the earthquake in the days of Uzziah
king of Judah uhhuh and the Lord my God
shall come and all the saints with thee
where you get these Saints from he told
you in first Thessalonians the 4th
chapter that the dead in Christ shall
rise so we're talking about the
resurrected Saints and we are talking
about the uh uh and those who are
changed who are righteous at the Lord's
coming there is no teaching the Rapture
Jesus never mentioned the disciple never
backed that up it is not scriptural it
is a Catholic doctrine of error I hope
that helped and as for the D behind you
could be if you rightous you gonna be uh
uh good grief you gonna get your
glorified body yeah you're not you're
not GNA be changed when you come it's
all that simple I hope that helps yeah
hey uh brother Julius in that in that
Matthew 24 they had in there can we read
that 40 and 41 and then you just expound
on that because she was asking too which
one is better better to be left or
taken so let's go to Matthew 24 and uh
10 read that 40 and 41 and then brother
Julius to take it from now which one is
better to be left or
taken okay Matthew 24 pick it up at
verse 40 then shall two be in the field
the one shall be taken and the other
left two women shall be grinding at the
meal the one shall be taken and the
other left it is the
resurrection it's the resurrection that
is not a Rapture that's the
resurrection we got lessons on
that keep watching Israel of God we got
lessons on
that
so it' be better to be taken than to be
left right brother we let the guest
caller expound okay guest caller yes sir
the ones that's the ones that's taken
are the ones that meeting the Lord in
the air yes sir
God and the one left behind of the
people that didn't make the change at
the first resurrection then they will
live on into the Millennium period when
Jesus going to rule for a thousand years
AB is the one in there and they came
back and the one that's left the one
that was still flesh and blood and
wasn't Chang and did not meet the Lord
in half okay yes right thank you right
so so to answer your question too it is
better to be taken and to be
left all right let's move on to our next
question sister moving on She also asked
in Genesis 1 uh what was the difference
between the light created in verses 3
and five and the light created in verses
14-
17 all right so brother let's go to
Genesis
1 and then you can pick it up at verse
three
and the guest car would take it from
there and God
see and God said let there be light and
there was
light and God saw the light that it was
good and God divided the light from the
darkness and God called the light day in
the darkness he called night in the
evening and the morning were the first
day
now skip down to verse
14 you and read
it and God said let there be lights in
the firmament of the heaven to divide
the day from the night and let them be
for signs and for seasons and for days
and
years and let them be for the lights in
the firmament of of the heaven to give
light upon the Earth and it was
so and God made two great lights the
greater light to Rule the Day and the
Lesser light to the night and he made
the Stars
also now now what verse was that you
read that was the end of
16 I want you to read
14 okay okay these are the two
difference you know uh uh uh these
lights came from different sources okay
and they and they were the light up
different
locations now we're going to look at and
and one was in the third
that was uh Genesis 1 you know uh
3-5
Genesis and was the third heaven and uh
and that light ain't no man
see and it and uh uh uh uh and and the
moon and the sun was not even mentioned
neither the Stars let's go and look at
it let's go into uh uh because this is
the light where no man can be let's go
to First Timothy 6th chapter read verses
13-
16 first Timothy
6 13 through
16 and I give thee charge in the sight
of God who Quicken all things and before
Christ Jesus who before ponan pilot
witness a confession
that thou keepest this commandment
without spot unrebuked until the
appearing of our Lord Jesus Christ which
in his times he shall show who is the
blessed and only Pon ponent the king of
kings and Lord of
lords who only
have as poent king of King and Lord of
lords go ahead and read who only have
immortality dwelling in
the look at this who only have
immortality Jesus is and let's see where
he and where is he dwelling go
ahead dwelling in the light which no man
can approach unto whom no man have seen
nor can see to whom be honor and power
Everlasting
amen so now that is the third heaven no
man have seen it no man can see it and
no man will see it that light that is
the one that the Lord created yes
first okay that's the one that verse
three and five is about now let's look
at this other source of light and see
what it gave light to so now we're going
to go to Genesis 14 and we're going to
read through to
17 go ahead when you get there and God
said let there be lights in the
firmament of the heaven to divide the
day from the night and let the let them
be for signs and for season and for days
and
years
let that's verse 14 and let them be for
lights in the firmament of the heaven to
give light upon the Earth and it was so
and God made two great lights the
greater light three there's three
Heavens now this form of the heaven is
under a body of water because the Lord
separated the water from the water right
with the firmament he all that fir with
heaven now he he then now he put uh some
lights in this firmament go
ahead and God made two great lights the
greater light to Rule the Day and the
Lesser light to rule the night he made
the Stars also and God set them in the
firmament of the heaven to give light
upon the
Earth go
ahead and to rule over the day and over
the night and to divide the light from
the darkness and God saw that it was
good and the evening and the morning
were the fourth
day now the first light can't nobody uh
uh no man can uh uh uh see that light
they can't even get to that light never
will but this light which broke which
was to put light on the on the Earth all
men see it every time the sun come up
every time the day break every man in
the creation who's not blind sees it
but the other light which is the third
heaven where F where Jesus and the
father and the angels dwell no man is
ever seen that light there's a big body
of water
between the uh uh lights in the
firmament which is the sun moon and
stars and the light where God
is third heaven that's the two different
one was to put light upon the earth and
the other was was to put light
create light in the third heaven which
no man can go where Jesus is right now
in the father that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
our next
question next question uh Sanders hering
says in 1 John 4: 18 are we not to fear
the lord and he gives Ecclesiastes 12
verse3
and Psalms
103: 11 and
17 all right brother Jerome what you got
for
that for
sure it will be in your best CES that
have a fear of the Lord but let's go
read those verses that you gave let's go
to First John chapter 4 verse
18 let me get it go ahead and read it
first John 4 verse
18 yes there is no fear in love but
perfect love casteth out fear because
fear ha torment he that fearth is
made is not made perfect in love okay
now the other two verses was
Ecclesiastes chap 12 verse
13 let us the conclusion of the whole
matter fear God and keep his
Commandments for this is the whole duty
of man and Psalms
103 verse 11 then skip to verse
17 Psalm
103:1 yeah for as a heaven is high above
the Earth so great is his Mercy towards
them that fear Him verse seven uh 17
but the mercy of the Lord is from
Everlasting to Everlasting upon them
that fear him and his righteousness unto
children's
children okay now uh in that first John
4 and the other two verses that we just
read the fear in in those three places
they're not the same okay the fear that
you read in 1 John 4:18 okay that fear
has to do with loving your neighbor like
Jesus love us there's no fear in love
all right there's no torment in that
love because you loving your neighbor
like you love yourself okay now that's
different from the fear that you have
for God okay and that's what those other
two verses is about that Ecclesiastes
and that Psalms 103 so now look let's
look at example of that fear okay
because that fear you should have
all right Exodus
20 pick it up at the 18 and read it to
the
20 and all the people saw the Thunder
and the lightning and the noise of the
trumpet the mountain smoked and when the
people saw it they removed them and
stood a far off they said unto Moses
speak thou with us we will hear but let
not God speak with us L we die and Moses
said unto the people fear not for God
has come to prove you and that his fear
may be before your faces that you sin
not so don't be afraid to trust God but
at the same time the fear of the Lord
needs to be there so that you don't sin
against them right that's the difference
okay that's all I got
on all right thank you for that hope
that answered their question as we move
on sister with a Time Check Yes the time
is
756 uh prayer Warrior ask for you
to ask for you to shed some light on
Malachi 3 vers 3 and
17 is this meaning punishment until per
action all right why don't we go there
Malachi
3 and verse three and verse
17 and go ahead brother the guest caller
will take it from there Malachi 3 and
3 Malachi 3
and3
yes and he shall sit as a refiner and
purifier of silver he shall purify the
sons of Le and purge them as gold and
silver that they may offer unto the Lord
an offering in
righteousness now that is when the Lord
returned and he is going to reinstate
the levitical priesthood let's go to
Ezekiel the 44th chapter and read verses
10 and
11 and the Levites that are gone away
far from me when Israel went astray
which went astray away from me after
their Idols they shall even bear their
iniquities yet they shall be ministers
in My Sanctuary having charges at the
gates of the house and ministering to
the house they shall slay the burnt
offering and the sacrifice for the
people and they shall stand before them
to minister unto
them now and let you know so when the
Lord bring the Levites back he going to
purify them and clean them up and give
them the job back and will do what they
was doing before he uh uh before he uh
uh terminated animal
sacrifice why he's reinstating that you
got to ask him that when he come but he
going to bring the the the Levites back
you're going to purify them and they
going to start doing animal sacrifice
and offerings just like they did before
the New Covenant now let's read in uh uh
uh let's get to verse 17
and it shall come to pass that when they
enter in the gates just eel 44 and 17
right no no go back to Malachi 3 and
17 and they shall be mine say the Lord
of hosts in that day when I make up my
jewels and I will spare them as a man
spare of his own son that serveth
him now that's
uh was that just the 17th verse right
right okay let's back up to 16 and find
out what this really talking about how
what the God is talking about now read
verse 16 and
17 then they that fear the lord spake
often one to another and the Lord
hearkened and heard it and the Book of
remembrance was written before him for
them that fear the lord and that thought
upon his name and they shall be mine say
the Lord of hosts and th day would I
make up my jewels and I will spare them
as a man spare of his own son that
serveth
him now he said Lord looked down on
Heaven he saw and all of those were
speaking in his name and Gathering
Together his name he wrote their name in
a book he called one name for what he
call a book of remembrance so when he
come he said they going to be him a SP
him it's like a man sp's own son now
let's go let's take another look at this
book let's go into Luke the 10th
chapter and we're going to read verse 17
through
20 and the 70 returned again with Joy
saying Lord even the devils are subject
unto us through thy name
and he said unto them I beheld Satan is
lightning fall from
Heaven behold he people he he sent out
70 uhh uh disciples he gave him power to
do you know D out devils and everything
else and they was really uh uh surprised
because they said Lord even the Devils
uh uh subject to us in our name cuz they
was casting out devils and everything
else but then what did the Lord say go
ahead
behold I give unto you power to tread on
serpents and scorpions and over all the
power of the enemy and nothing shall by
any means hurt you notwithstanding in
this Rejoice not that the spirits are
subject unto you but rather Rejoice
because your names are written in
heaven so now why were they name where
were when were they name written in
heaven that's when the Lord look down
and saw the that spoke often in his name
he wrote them in the book so where is
the book now the book is in heaven with
the Lord now Israel Sinn against the
Lord and Moses went and Moses made a
request to the Lord if he don't forgive
their sins let's go look at it let's go
into uh
uh let's go into uh uh uh Exodus the 20
32nd chapter Exodus chapter
32 and we're going to read
31-33 verses 31 through
33 and Moses returned unto the Lord and
said oh this people have sinned a great
sin and have made them gods of gold yet
now If thy will forgive their sin and if
not blot me now pray thee out of thy
book which thou H has
written talking about he wrote your name
in it but then Moses said if you want
forgive sin to get a sin the people
write me out of that book Moses know he
was in that book but what did the Lord
say and the Lord said unto Moses
whosoever have sinned against me him
would I blot out of my
book oh so who whosoever sin against him
him will have BL out of his book what
book was that the book of memers what
else is that book called let's go to
Revelation 20th chapter Revelation the
30 chapter rather and read verse five 3
and
five he that overcometh the same shall
be clothed in white rain now will not
block out his name out of the book of
life but I
will that book of remembrance is called
a book of life that's
right now let's let's see what happened
if you're not in that book SK down let's
go to Revelation 20 we're going to read
verses 11 12 and
15 Revelation 20 11 and 12
first and I saw a great white throne and
him that sat on it from whose the face
of the earth and the heaven fled away
and there was found no place for them
and I saw the dead small and great stand
before God and the books were open and
another book was open which is The Book
of
Life Same Book of Life get down and go
ahead finish that and then Skip and the
dead were judged out of those things
which were written in the books
according to their works
uhhuh I skip down to 15 and read it and
whosoever was not found written in the
Book of Life was cast into the Lake of
Fire so this book that the Lord looked
down and he wrote your name in it which
he called the book of remembrance is The
Book of Life and you could be in it but
if you sin against God you can get
blotted out of it and if you're not in
the book at the end of the Judgment
you're going to to the lake of fly
right yeah Book of Life is an important
place to be most important all right
hope that answered your question there
as we move on to our next question next
question uh Casey being asked is it a
pagan practice to hold hands while
praying my children and I often do
this the Pagan if you're holding hands
while you praying what you say
Dre
no no listen you are
praying look in in fact in 1 Samuel the
first chapter verses 12 and
13 Hannah prayed in her heart in her
mind only her lips moved but words
wasn't
heard Daniel kneel down now and he
prayed three times a
day
Jesus fell on his face and he prayed in
Matthew 26 and
39 Solomon spread forth his hands and
First Kings 8 and
22 and he
prayed the word don't say anything
about holding hands praying or not
holding hands praying
what it does say is
pray let's go to ma uh James the 5th
chapter there's nothing wrong with
praying James 5 pick it up at 13 brother
go ahead when you get it if any among
you Afflicted let him pray is in he
mared let him sing ssongs listen if you
afflicted pray right the book tell you
to bring your children up in the way
that they shall go prayer is one of them
ways that they shall
go if you hold in hands with them pray
with them
right all that stuff if people looking
for something wrong why don't they look
for something right you are bringing
your children up in the way that they
shall go go ahead
brother is any sick among you let him
call for the Elders of the church and
let them pray over
him anoint him with oil in the name of
the Lord and the prayer of faith shall
save the sick and the Lord shall raise
him up and if he have committed sins
they shall be forgiven him that's right
go ahead confess your faults one to
another and pray one for another that ye
may be healed they affect your fervent
prayer of a righteous man of ail of much
that avails much the prayer of the
righteous Avail much so keep praying
however you do it pray and then be
righteous walking in that word and teach
your children the same I hope that
helps yeah and sometimes it shows Unity
it shows Unity yeah yeah so all that
other I wouldn't even be concerned about
somebody may
say
okay all right thank you for that hope
that answered their question sister
Deborah next one next one CeCe asks when
we get baptized are we cleansed from all
sin yeah when you get baptized right
indeed you are you you you you're
cleansed from sin let's go in uh Acts
the second
chapter acts the 2
chapter because there's some
requirements for getting
baptized men have to be
circumcised women can't be on their
monthly and and Etc and other things but
uh pick it up at that verse uh 38
brother read 38 and 39 go
ahead then Peter said unto them repent
and be baptized every one of you in the
name of Jesus Christ for the remission
of sins and ye shall receive the gift of
the Holy Ghost that's another
requirement repent be sorry for all them
sins you committed and when you're going
to get baptized and you know what you
was doing was against the Lord you stop
doing that after you get baptized verse
39 for the promise is unto you and to
your children and to all that are far
off even as many as the Lord our God
shall call and this is required of
everybody black white young poor Rich or
old doesn't matter and when you gladly
receive that word and ready ready to
change your ways verse
41 then they that GL gladly receive his
word were
baptized and the same day there were
added unto them about 3,000 Souls yeah
turn over to Romans the 6th
chapter because when you getting
baptized you enter into a covenant with
the Lord who died for the sins of the
whole world and you shouldn't be doing
the same things that's against God after
you come up out of that water shouldn't
be maintained in those things you should
wash them away that's what the baptism
is about washing away the old
sand Romans 6 and pick it up at verse
three
brother know ye not that so many of us
as we're baptized into Jesus Christ
we're baptized into his death
y therefore we are buried with them by
baptism into death that like as Christ
was raised up from the dead by the glory
of the father even so we also should
walk in newness of life so when you come
up out that water you do this thing and
this walk with God with all your might
you have already repented and been
baptized in the name of Jesus which is
also key read that verse
six knowing this that our old man is
crucified with him that the body of sin
might be destroyed that hence not serve
sin right but righteousness that's what
you are required to serve when you're
talking about getting baptized skip down
read that last verse for
me read that verse
13 neither yield ye your members as
instrument of unrighteousness Unto sin
but yield your elves unto God as those
that are alive from the dead and your
members it as instruments of
righteousness unto God yeah so you know
once you come up out that water then you
are saying with the Lord that you're
going to walk in righteousness put that
sin aside and you GNA be joyful that he
has even called you into the word to
even get baptized so when you got
baptized right yeah all that sin is put
aside just walk this walk or run this
race with all your might that's all I
got hey Cornell on their own they can
read that Luke
7:47 Jesus told that woman your sins
which are many are
forgiven yeah that's the fairness of God
brother indeed he is very merciful all
right hope that ansed your question and
let us move on to our next one uh moving
on the Holder Family Tree says I have a
child that is 5 years old if we send him
to school during the high days are we in
violation of Leviticus 23 making
teachers bus drivers Etc have to
work all right brother Jerome what you
say about
that well you
got seven annual half sabbaths and um
Passover is a sabath uh is a u Memorial
it's not it's it's not a
Sabbath all right even though it's a
high feast day okay now as far as the
other
ones I'd like to make a suggestion um
maybe you could make Provisions with
your teacher with the teacher your your
child's teacher you know about getting
the uh
assignments that the teacher will be giv
on that day you would like to have your
child at home to keep the the high day
and the teacher might be willing to do
that for you and then the Lord will see
that and I'm I I bet you he'll be real
pleased with that you know um that's a
suggestion I will make and as far as
um your child um making the
teacher U work or the bus drive
work they going to do that whether you
bring your child to school or not you
know so they not making them work they
going to continue to work whether your
child is there or not but uh with all
your heart mind soul and strength try to
keep the Commandment even when it comes
to your children so make some make that
kind of effort and if the teacher go
along with it praise God he he ple with
that that anybody want to ask something
they
can y like you said brother Dre pray
pray pray right
right all right hope that ansed your
question as we move on to our next one
next one sister Israel ask in the book
of habaka chapter 3 verse one is shal a
musical term or nation and was habaka
praying about Al the end
times share some light on habaka there
brother
Julius let's go to that scripture habca
3 And1 Tel habca 3 and one the
definition of shigar is a musical term
and it means it's a prayer that is set
to music and the prayer is a very
emotional uh when you're praying with
strong emotional but you're doing it in
song it's like some of the Psalms that
David did
read Get It Go ahead and read it hebecca
3 And1 a prayer of hebecca the prophet
of PR
Sho that's all it means it means that
he's doing a prayer that's accompanied
by music that music can be soft it could
be loud it could be emphatic but it's a
strong prayer that's set written to
music that's all it is it's like the
Psalms so it is a musical term yes
that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
hope that answerers their question as we
continue to move
on moving on Zion says I try to tell my
sister that the Sabbath is on a Saturday
she says if God only said she says God
only said first day second day and so
forth no one knows since the name of the
days were manmade how can I explain
it all right brother Julius can you help
her sister to get some clarity on the
Sabbath day okay you can't say that no
one knows because everything that's the
Lord wanted us to know he had it
written so the the days that we have are
Roman or Latin okay we have a weak cycle
but the Lord set the weak cycle in force
and you read Genesis the 1st chapter you
read all the way down to the uh 31st
verse let's get there Genesis uh 1 and
31 when you get it go ahead brother
Genesis 1 and
31 these days are named after Roman uh
Gods and
planets the day that we have but the
Lord number his days go ahead
brother and God saw everything that he
had made and behold it was very good and
the evening and the morning were the
sixth day and go ahead into Genesis
chapter 2 verse one go ahead thus the
Heaven and the Earth were Fin and all
the hosts of them uhhuh and on the seven
day God ended his work which he had made
uhuh he rested on the seventh day from
all his work which he had made go ahead
and God blessed the seven day and
Sanctified it because that in it he had
rested from all his work which God
created and made now let's look at what
God
called the seventh
day let's go to Exodus the 20th
chapter let's see who doing this
speaking
here exus 20 brother tenzel we gonna
read verses one and then skip when you
get it go ahead brother and God spake
all these words saying so now God is
speaking all these words the Lord spoke
these words out of his mouth
verse eight skip down to verse eight and
continue remember the Sabbath day to
keep it holy yes six days shall thy laen
do all thy work but the seven day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God and it thou
shall not do any work thou nor that son
nor th daughter that man servant nor
that maid servant nor that cattle nor
that stranger that within thy
gates6 now the book tells you that God
said this he said but the seventh day is
the Sabbath now the Latin word or the
Roman word for Saturn is
sabbaton okay but that's in Latin in
English we call it the Sabbath but it
still means they arrest go ahead and
read at verse
14 thou not commit adultery no verse 14
brother um verse 11 verse 11 for six
days the Lord made Heaven and Earth the
sea and all that in them is and rested
the seventh day wherefore the Lord
blessed the sabath day and hollowed it
same thing we read in Genesis chapter 2
the Lord blessed the seventh day and
hallowed it and named it the Sabbath day
the rest of the days he numbered one
through six God numbered them one
through six right but the Romans came
along and they gave them Sunday Monday
Tuesday Wednesday Sunday after the Sun
Monday named after the Moon Third Day
name after Mars fourth day Mercury fifth
day Venus this but the Saturn the
Sabbath day remain sabbaton and that's
what the in the Latin that's what it
means so that's all I got Cornel so God
named the Sabbath day so it is you are
correct sister the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord and the Lord tell
you that the seventh day is that mean
that is a direct definition of the
seventh day day rest that's all I got
Cornel
yes sir you're correct brother even when
Jesus was in the flesh he came and he
taught in the synagogues on the Sabbath
day that's right the fourth chapter Luke
chapter 4 as his custom was he went in
the sabath synagogue on the Sabbath day
and stood up for read a day of worship
and a day of rest that's right and the
Christians follow
Jesus all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our
next moving on Mur says can you explain
Proverbs 11
ver10 also when Peter stood and spoke to
the people in Jerusalem in Acts 2
verse5 was it just men there or was it
also
women all right so we going there
Proverbs 11 And1
first yes and then at Acts 2 and5 but
let's go to that Proverbs 11
and10 and the guest call let take it
from
there that's Proverbs 11 and 10
yes when it goeth well with the
righteous the city rejoiceth and when
the wicked perish there is
shouting now let's show you what what
this mean let's go into proverb the 29th
chapter and read verse two
Proverbs 29
verse2 well the righteous are in
Authority the people Rejoice but when
the wicked beareth rule the people
mourn okay have a righteous person in
Char people are happy but when you have
the wicked in charge They Mourn and and
U and now when he done he
Rejoice because the uh because he you
know because he won't be able to hurt
him
anymore now let's go and uh uh deal with
the other one acts 2
and5 and there were dwelling at jerus at
Jerusalem Jews devout men out of every
nation under
heaven now the question is was there uh
any women there let's go into Acts 2 and
read verse five and we going to go a
little further well you just read it 2
and five but let's go to Deuteronomy the
16th
chapter and we going to read verse 10
and
11 16 verse
10 and
11 and thou shall keep the feix of weeks
unto the Lord thy God with the tribute
of a free will offering of thy hand
which Thou shalt give unto the Lord thy
God according as the Lord thy God hath
blessed thee and thou shall rejoice
before the Lord thy God thou and thy son
and thy daughter and thy manservant and
thy maid servant and the Levites that is
within thy Gates and the stranger and
the fatherless and the Widow that are
among you in the place which the Lord
thy God hath chosen to place his name
there so what is the Feast of Weeks
Pentecost ain't that correct
that's
right that's sir we had plenty of women
there don't you
yeah okay that's
all all right hope that answers your
question there we move on to our next
one next question Gilbert a asks when do
you know God wants you to move on from a
certain
situation not meaning love like
something you're doing in
life all right there's a few variables
to that but what you say
Dre yeah when do you know I mean you
know to move on from something you're
doing in life when you know it goes
against the word of
God let's go over to Micah the 6th
chapter Micah
6 when you know better you do
better and when you know what you should
and shouldn't do you you don't do what
you shouldn't do and you do what you
should Micah 6 and read verse eight
brother go
ahead he have showed thee oh man what is
good and what do the Lord require of
thee but to do justly and to love mercy
and to walk humbly with thy God this is
what the Lord wants us to do he has
showed us what is
good now let's let's go to Romans 7 we
going to read verse 12 and see what is
good just in case we don't know let's
see what Romans 7 and 12 say is good go
ahead when you get it brother read that
wherefore the law is Holy and the
Commandment holy and just and good that
is what is Holy just and good the
Commandment now let's go to the last
place let's go to James 4 and
7 James 4 and
7 now is that James 4 and 17 I'm sorry 4
and
17 go ahead brother so therefore to him
that knoweth to do good and doeth it not
to him it is sin M so that's when you
know you should move on from a
situation like you said not meaning love
like something you doing in life you
move on for something that you doing in
life when you know it goes against the
word of God because to know to do good
and do it not to him it is sin that's
all I
got all
right hope answered your question there
as we continue to move on to our next
question next question we can talk right
here as for you to explain first Peter
3: 19 and
20 1 Peter 3 19 and 20 all right why
don't we go there brother tanzel and
read
that go ahead my
brother by which also he went preach
unto the spirits in prison which
sometime were
disobedient when Once the long suffering
of God waited into the days of Noah
while the ark was of preparing wherein
few that is eight Souls were saved by
water yeah so in verse 19 where it talks
about they were in prison just saying
that they were under chains of Darkness
that you wouldn't be able to to see them
we can't see them but we know the Lord
can
by which also he went in preaching to
the spirits in prison let's go to Second
Peter 2 and read that one verse four for
they are in Chains of
Darkness second Peter 2 and verse
four yes
sir whereby are given unto us exceeding
great and precious promises that by
these you might partakers of the divine
nature having second Peter you in second
Peter
2 yeah second verse
second for if God Spar not the angels
that sin but cast them down to Hell and
deliver them into chains of Darkness to
be re reserved unto judgment so that
chains of Darkness that's what that
prison was that we talking about in that
verse 19 now go back to that 1 Peter 3
and and read that 20 cuz all the Lord
was telling them to just you know pull
back relax with all this destruction you
don't be patient there's only eight
Souls here at this time go
ahead which sometime were disobedient
when Once the long suffering of God
waited into the days of Noah while the
ark Was preparing wherein few that his
eight Souls were saved by water right so
it was only eight Souls at this time the
Lord had when and preach to them them
Unholy Angels telling them to relax and
chill pull back that destruction was
only eight people here hey You' be
turned loose again but that wasn't the
time right there that's all I
got all right hope that answered your
question let's keep it moving with a
time check sis yes time 8:30 Jun nor for
asks how do you destroy your temple
how do you destroy your temple that body
of yours J Rome how do you
destroy simply put it to disobey
God but I'm going give you some verses
let's go to Second Corinthians chapter
6 we going to read Verse 16-
18 you get it go ahead and read
second Corin 2 Corinthians
16-8 and what agreement have the temple
of God with Idols for ye are the Temple
of the Living God as God have said I
will dwell in them and walk in them and
I will be their God and they shall be my
people so wherefore come out from among
them and be ye separated sayth the Lord
and touch not the unclean thing and I
will receive you and will be a father
unto you and ye shall be my sons and
daughters sayeth the Lord allmighty yeah
so let the word of God separate you
sanctify you
okay it said be separate that's right
let's go to uh Hebrews chapter
10 and we going to pick up pick it up at
uh 15 and 16 we going to
here Hebrews 10 verse 15-
16 go ahead whereof the Holy Ghost also
is a witness to us for after that he has
said before this is the Covenant that I
will make with them after those days
sayth the Lord I will put my laws into
their hearts and into their minds while
I write them we talking New Covenant
here skip down to verse 26 and read it
to the 27
for if we sin willfully after that we
have received the knowledge of the truth
there remaineth no more sacrifice for
sins but a certain fearful looking for
of judgment and fiery indignation which
shall Devour the adversary that'll be
the ultimate destruction of your temple
okay that's all I got on
it all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered their question as we
sister Deborah we going into new
territory now uh yes we are uh we are
now into tonight's Q&A for October the
2024 and Miss way says in Hosea 2 verse
16 what did God mean
when with what did God mean with Thou
shalt not call me
bail all right what did God mean when he
said he didn't want us call him ba let's
go to that Hosea 2 and16
and and the guest caller would take it
from
there and it shall be at that day sayeth
the Lord that thou shall call me ishi
and shall call me no more
baa okay is mean my husband but the
people when they went into the land
that's why the Lord wanted Israel when
he said I want you to go into the land I
don't want you to make no le with these
people set on their altars bur up the
gods and everything else because and
leave none of them living because if you
don't they going to turn you against me
and so that is actually what Israel did
they start serving other God and the
angel warned them first let's go to
judges 2 and verse
one we're going to read this about two
three verses then we going to
skip J just
two an angel the
Lord goad and the angel of the Lord came
up from gilgal Tobin and said I made you
to go up out of Egypt and have brought
you into the land which I swear unto
your fathers and I said I will never
break my Covenant with
you and you shall make no lead with the
inhabitants of this land you shall throw
down their altars but ye have not obeyed
my voice why have ye done
this wherefore I said wherefore I also
said I will not drive them out from
before you but they shall be as thorns
in your side and their gods shall be a
snare unto
you now that's what he told him now he
want you to do that don't make no kind
of C cuz if you don't you're going to be
a thorn in your side they God going to
be a snare and that's exactly what it
was skip down to verse 12 read verse 12
and
13 and they forsook the Lord God of
their fathers which brought them out of
the land of Egypt and followed other
gods of the Gods of the people that were
round about them and and bowed thems
unto them and provoked the Lord to
anger and they forsook the Lord and
served baale and astero and the anger of
the Lord was hot against Israel and he
delivered
them now bill was one of the names of
the Canaanite Pagan God had had the uh
uh Bill and you had ASA and several more
so now they replaced their
God With canit's God one of them being
baale and they start call on the name of
instead of the name of God but when
Jesus come back he said you and I'm
going to marry you you going to call me
my husband and you ain't going you call
me baale no more that's the Pagan God
that they were serving because they had
replaced the Lord with canaan's
God the B was never lord's name it was
the name of a one of the canite pagans
go that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question there as we move on to our next
one with the time check yes the time is
837 ah
says God had given Satan permission to
Temp Joe is it possible that God gave
Satan permission to enter the Garden of
Eden and test Adam and
Eve Satan was already there in the in
the Garden of Eden with Adam and Eve and
with the Lord himself so when it comes
to the word temp and test those words
are interchangeable sometime you can use
them to mean the same definition if you
tempted or if you test it sometimes it
can mean exact same thing but um when it
comes to being tempted or tested say is
no respect of person he would try you me
him her and anybody he can get his hands
on because he is a destroyer let's go
into that um first Peter first Peter
5 and let's pick it up at that verse 8 1
Peter 5 and read eight and nine let's
see what Satan job is
be sober be vigilant because your
adversary the devil as a roaring lion
walketh about seeking whom may
devour whom resist steadfast in the
faith knowing that the same afflictions
are accomplish in your brethren that are
in the world so he don't have no respect
to person anybody he can destroy he is
on them but it said that he the
adversary the Devil is a ruin lion
walking about seeking whom he may devour
and you can even go in Luke the 4th
chapter and read that he even came to
try and um tempt or test Jesus that's
right so who are we turn over brother to
um Hebrews the 4th
chapter Hebrews the 4th and when he
tempted Jesus let's see what happened
Hebrews the 4th chapter pick it up at
that verse 14 for me when you get there
seeing then that we have a great high
priest that has passed into the heavens
Jesus the son of God let us hold fast
our
profession for we have not high priest
which cannot be touched with a filling
of our infirmities but was in all points
temped like as we are yet without sin oh
so even Jesus was tempted and that Luke
the 4th chapter but yet without sin so
Satan is a Destroyer that is one of his
names now turn to that job right quick
turn to job and let's see this um good
report that job had here job the first
chapter and just read two verses for
me because this would be good and a good
report for any man or woman or child to
have right is what job was caring right
here job the first chapter and read that
verse one for me brother and then we go
to skip down and read eight and that'll
be it what what what it said about job
here go ahead there was a man in the
land of USS whose name was job and that
man was perfect and upright and one that
fearth God and it was evil one that
feared God and excused evil he hated
evil but he feared god what the Lord say
about him and a that be it and the Lord
said unto Satan hast thou considered my
servant joob there is none like him in
the earth a perfect and an upright man
one that fearth God and is cheth evil so
the Lord even said that about job that
he he know that he feared him and that
he hated evil and job went through a lot
of stuff but yet hey he had these good
characteristics on and read verse 22
when he was going through what he went
through in it's U chapter one go ahead
what's 22 say and in all this Jo sinth
not nor charge God foolishly yes so
sometime when we going through it we
just have to be strong stay prayed up to
the Lord but um you can be tempted or
tested at any time by anyone them evil
angels you just have to stay strong with
the Lord that's all I
got all right we hope that answered your
question let us move on sister Deborah
time is flying when you're having fun
yes Malik Shakur asked why in Matthew 28
verse
19 Jesus said go and baptize in the name
of the father and the Son and the Holy
Ghost but in Acts 2 verse
38 it says in the name of Jesus
Christ all right good question Sharon
lightone um we gonna go take a look at
it go to that Matthews 28 and and uh 19
and brother tanel we going to deal with
that acts
238 in a minute because I want some
verses before that
okay all right so read that Matthews
28:19 so go ye therefore and teach All
Nations baptizing them in the name of
the father and of the son and of the
Holy Ghost okay now I want you to pay
attention the Lord didn't tell you to
quote this
verse you know he said baptize in the
name not in the titles of the father son
or Holy Ghost right okay so the name is
not father the name is not son the name
is Jesus because that's the name that
the father gave to the son that's the
father's name okay and I'm going to show
you some verses where he said I came in
my father's name
right okay which is Jesus because that's
the name that the father gave the son
and that's the name that the Holy Ghost
is sent so when you call on the name of
Jesus you covering all three right right
so we got to stop quoting this verse and
actually do what he telling you to do
and that's the baptize in the name
that's why when you go in the uh in the
book of Acts and you see what the
apostles are doing when they baptizing
they're baptizing in the name of Jesus
right now let's go to let's go
to okay read the scripture who name came
in and what and who he send it his name
why don't you read it I think that's
that's a direct answer to the question
okay so uh let's go to John
43 that's
right yeah read that I don't come in my
father's name and ye receive me not if
another shall come in his own name him
ye will receive yeah you know and and as
far as the price part which is in that
acts 2 and 38 which you gave as a part
of your question let's go read
that when you get it go ahead and
read then Peter said unto them repent
repent and be baptized every one of you
in the name of Jesus Christ for the
remissions of sins and ye shall receive
the gift of the Holy Ghost now Christ
that's not a part of his name
Christ is what he is he's the anointed
one okay so Christ I think that's the
Greek word for anointed one
and uh the Hebrew word for anointed one
is Messiah so that's not his name that's
that's the title of him being an
anointed one Jesus is his name okay and
I ask some other verses but but for the
sake of time that's all I
got well sometime you need to lose some
time because I answer the question okay
and go to
Philippians uh how that Jesus given a
name above every
name than the three and start reading at
verse five
is that uh uh
phius yeah
two reading that
F let this mind being you which was also
in Christ Jesus who being in the form of
God thought in that robbery to be equal
with God but made himself of no
reputation and took upon him the form of
a servant and was made in the likeness
of
men and being F found in fashion as a
man he humbled himself and became
obedient unto death even the death of
the Cross wherefore God also have highly
exalted him and given him a name which
is above every name that at the name of
Jesus every knee should bow of things in
heaven and things in Earth and things
under the Earth and that every tongue
shall confess that Jesus Christ is Lord
to the glory of God the
father now so now when Jesus came he
gave him a name above every name he gave
him his own name that's why Jerome read
earlier where he said I come in my
father's name but now somebody grab
right quick and said he should pray to
the father and he going to send you the
Holy Ghost in his name St John chapter
26 for the comforter which is the Holy
Ghost whom the father will send in my
name he shall teach you all things and
bring all things to your remembrance
whatsoever I have said unto you so now
he said go baptized in the name of the
father Son and the Holy Ghost Jesus came
in the father's name that mean his name
was Jesus so now and also the father's
name was Jesus and then he said he going
to pray to the father and you going to
send you the Holy Ghost in his name
which was Jesus Jesus names so when you
uh baptize in the name of Jesus you
baptize it in the name of the father and
in the name of the son and in the name
of the Holy Ghost instead of quoting
them and quoting titles like Jerome said
father that's the man of everybody that
got a name and everybody got a child son
that's every male and the Holy Ghost
that's the spirit of God they come in
many forms that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we continue to move
on moving on Jacob Israel says I was
baptized in another Israelite Camp
should I get baptized in the
iog should I get re-baptized in the
iog if you were if you were at Israelite
camp where the truth was taught and you
met all the requirements to be baptized
and you was baptized in Jesus name um
guest caller can you us add on to
that that's if they baptize you in Jesus
name and you're another Israelite Camp
then there's no need for
it
okay all right we're gonna leave it
right there and keep right on moving yes
uh Sharon Jackson uh asks can you
explain why could tour Abraham's wife is
referred to as his wife in Genesis 25
verse1 but 1 Chronicles 32 calls her his
concubine also do we distinguish wives
from
concubines how do we distinguish wives
concubines Julius how do we do
that the difference is a concubine is
like a lesser wife she dwells with the
man but she doesn't have the same
equality as the as the main wife or wiv
that's the difference now let's go to
Genesis 25
23 Genesis
23 the book said in St John the 5th
chapter had you believe Moses you would
have believed me I'mma ride with
Moses Genesis 23 and pick it up at verse
one Tel Genesis 23 And1 this is Sarah
Abraham's first
wife will you go ahead brother and Sarah
was7 and 20 years old these were the
years of the life of Sarah uhhuh and
Sarah died in kjf arba the same is
Hebron in the land of Canaan and Abraham
came to mourn for Sarah and to weep for
her so now Sarah
died the thing that frees you from uh
marriage is death or adultery now let's
go to Genesis the 25th
chapter let's look at what the book
called uh called his uh his his second
wife when after Sarah died what the book
said verse
one then again Abraham took a wife and
her name was cout and what did he what
did Moses say right about this then
Abraham then again Abraham took a wife a
wife and her name was Cura the book
called her his wife now let's go to
First Chronicles and you wanted uh in
your uh statement you said uh what is
this first Chronicles 32 there's no 32
so we found your answer in 1 Chronicles
1 and
32 go ahead and
read okay 1 Chronicles 1 1 Chronicles 1
and verse 32
tenzel now the sons of cout Abraham's
concubine she bear zimran and Jin and
Madan and median and isback and shuah
the sons of jshin Sheba and Dean now the
translators they put conbine here but
the the scriptures in uh Genesis says
called Abraham Sarah uh K Cura his
Abraham's wife so again the
concubine in some terms in some
countries is used as a wife that is not
equal to the first wife or
wives but that word that's the term
concubine but the Bible calls uh CA
Abraham's wife I'mma ride with that
right that's all got yes sir good
explanation let's leave it right there
keep moving sister Deborah's time is a
ticket yes I ler says how could
dinosaurs exist before the sun and moon
were created as described in
Genesis Julius what you
say I say we got the fossil fossil and
we got the skeletons but you don't see
no descendants of dinosaurs here today
like we have uh like we see the
skeletons okay you don't see no uh uh
because that was not for our
creation Genesis the first chapter was
all this was created for our sun star
moons all the fossil fuel it's called
fossil fuel why where did it come from
dead trees plants and dinosaur bones let
me go to two scriptures because these
are it sound like to me somebody might
not
believe the evidence let's go to gen
Genesis 18th
chapter Genesis the 18th
chapter and this the best I can do for
this Cornel uh the book says in another
scriptures shall their unbelief make the
word of God a none
effect Genesis 18 and pick it up at
verse 10 Genesis 18 I believe this is
what I
want and let's look at because somebody
don't believe does not make it not true
go ahead and read Genesis 18-10 go ahead
and he said I will certainly return unto
thee according to the time of light and
lo Sarah thy wife shall have a son and
sever heard it in the tent door which
was behind him and what did Sarah do at
verse 12 she didn't believe God verse 12
go ahead therefore Sarah alive within
herself saying after I am wax old shall
I have pleasure my Lord being also old
uhhuh now Sarah's old past bearing a
child but God said you gonna have a
child next year at this time verse 13 go
ahead the Lord said unto Abraham
wherefore this Sarah Li saying shall I
have surely bear a child which am old
what did what did the Lord respond go
ahead is anything too hard for the Lord
the time pointed I will return unto thee
according to the time of life and Sarah
sh have a son is anything too hard for
the Lord let's read it again Jeremiah
the 32nd chapter and I'll be done with
this right here Jeremiah chapter
32 we don't have no dinosaur today
because the Lord used those beasts and
that at that time uh whenever it was to
prep the Earth for man like he's
prepping the Earth right now he going
prep the Earth for Spirit beings
right Genesis 32 we going to read verse
26 and
27 Genesis 32 26 and 27 when you get it
tzel go ahead and
read Genesis 32 Jeremiah Jeremiah 32
Jeremiah
32 26 and 27 I gotta put my glasses
on Jeremiah 3226 and
27 then came the word of the Lord unto
Jeremiah saying behold I am the Lord thy
God of All Flesh is there anything too
hard for me behold I'm the I am the Lord
the God of All Flesh is there anything
too hard for
me because you don't believe hey we
breathing air but we can't see it that's
right but the bottom line is the Lord
said is anything too hard for me
dinosaurs existed they are still go to
Arizona go to Las Vegas they still are
digging and finding fossils for things
that existed they are finding fish at
the fish fossils at the top of mountains
when the floods came down when the
waters receded the uh bones and
everything fossil lies to leave evidence
that there was something here before man
that's why he told he told man multiply
be fruitful and replenish the Earth
that's right that's all I got to us
brother Corel
hey I believe it with everything with
them I believe this
book I want to
give direct answer to that question is
they existed because God wanted them to
exist point blank Point
Blank all right hope that answered your
question next question as we come down
to our last one maybe two what is it
yeah all right next question Roger K
says can you explain how the cross is a
form of
idolatry how is the cross a form of
idolatry brother
Dre yeah idolatry is is coming from idol
worship when you have an object of
worship and people worship the cross now
let's go to Exodus the 20th chapter
Exodus
20 and pick it up at verse three and
read three to five real
quick go ahead and get it when you when
you get it go ahead and read brother
quick as you can thou have no other gods
before me thou sh make any Graven image
or any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in the water under
the Earth thou shall not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them why the
Lord th God I'm a jealous God okay hold
on that is enough
this is happens with the
cross with the image that they have on
the cross they bow down they kiss it it
is a form of idolatry because they
worshiping but not only that let's go to
Ezekiel 8 right quick Ezekiel 8 and we
gonna pick it up at verse
10 Ezekiel
8 and 10 go ahead and read it when read
nine and 10 go ahead brother said unto
me go in and Behold The Wicked
Abomination that they do here so I went
in and saw and behold every form of
creeping things and abominable beasts
and all the idols of the House of Israel
betrayed upon the walls round about so
they got all these Idols portrayed on
the walls round about now skip down to
verse 15 go ahead then say he unto meast
thou seen this oh son of man turn thee
yet again and thou shal shall see
greater Abominations than these said
have you seen this old son of man I'mma
show you greater Abominations bag up and
read verse 14 because this is the
Abomination that he speaks of go ahead
this is one of them go ahead and he
brought me to the door of the gate to
the Lord's House which was towards the
North and behold there sat woman weeping
for Tomas now I want you to look up
tamuz and the symbol for moves on your
own and when you see what it is you
would not ask that question again go
ahead brother read verse
16 and he brought me into the inner
Court of the Lord's House and behold at
the door the Temple of the Lord between
the porch and the altar were about five
and 20 men and their backs was toward
the Temple of the Lord and their faces
toward the East and they worship the sun
towards the east so this mes is dealing
with that symbol that you talking about
this cross and Sun worship Sunday but
the cross itself was a symbol of death
many people died on the cross it was a
it was a torture symbol it had nothing
to do with worship it is a Graven image
as we read in Exodus 20 and we should
not do it I hope that
helps yes sir Dre it was a it was a
Roman death symbol too wasn't it it was
crucifying people on the cross before
Christ even came on the
scene yeah so yeah truly Pagan and and
it shouldn't be worn right
brother that's right all right sister
Deborah what's our
time uh the time is
9:02 oh we done ran out of
time but we want to say to everybody
that's out there want to thank you for
tuning in with us from all around the
world and if you submitted a question
and we didn't have a chance to get to it
we will address that question next week
at the same time sister Deborah is going
to take that question put it in rotation
and we will deal with it in then so
please don't resubmit your question we
will deal with it next week so until we
all come together again
want to thank you all and we say be safe
and be blessed and may the Lord have
mercy on us all brother tanzel as you
close us up Our Father which are in
heaven Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom
come thy will be done in earth as it is
in heaven give us this day our daily
bread and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debtors and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the the glory forever in Jesus name we
pray amen